<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>



    <integer-array name="instruction_page_num" num="8">
        <item >6</item>
        <item >4</item>
        <item >2</item>
        <item >1</item>
        <item >1</item>
        <item >2</item>
        <item >4</item>
        <item >1</item>
    </integer-array>
    <array name="pages_1_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page1_icon1</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page1_icon2</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page1_icon3</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page1_icon4</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page1_icon5</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page1_icon6</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="pages_1_labels">
        <item >"Adjust font size"</item>
        <item >"Adjust phone volume"</item>
        <item >"Volume key plus switch machine key screenshot"</item>
        <item >"Intelligent Body Sense"</item>
        <item >"Quickly find apps"</item>
        <item >"Discover boutique applications in the application market"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages_1_desc">
        <item > "Open settings, click to display-> Font and display size, drag the control bar to adjust the display effect. "</item>
        <item > "Press the phone volume key to turn on the sound adjustment slider, you can adjust the video, music volume, adjust the call volume, switch call reminder mode, call ringtone, alarm clock volume and other volume settings. "</item>
        <item > "At the same time press the volume under the key to add the switch key, intercept the current screenshot, after the screenshot can be viewed in the gallery to view the intercepted picture. "</item>
        <item > "Set the-> Gesture-> Smart body sense to set gesture recognition, the coupon state in the screen to draw the corresponding gestures to quickly open the app ".</item>
        <item > "Search the box in the home screen to enter the name of the app you want to find, you can quickly find." In addition to apps, you can also search for settings items, contacts, and so on. "</item>
        <item > "Discover more, experience more, open the Google App market and experience boutique apps."</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="pages_2_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page2_icon1</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page2_icon2</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page2_icon3</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page2_icon4</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="pages_2_labels">
        <item > "Blur the background, highlight the theme "</item>
        <item >"Easily shoot gorgeous night scenes"</item>
        <item > "Smart camera, take a good picture with one click "</item>
        <item > "Cloud Map library, multi-device sharing "</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages_2_desc">
        <item > "Turn on the camera, click on the big aperture, tap the screen to select the focus theme "</item>
        <item > "Break through the weak light and dark bottleneck, enhance brightness and color, perfect display of screen details "</item>
        <item > "Turn on the camera, in photo mode, the camera will automatically select the most appropriate shooting mode based on the scene and object you are shooting, so that you can easily take good photos. "</item>
        <item > "Sign in to all devices on the same Google account to see photos and videos synced to the cloud library without worrying about photos and videos taking up device space and losing them." </item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="pages_3_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page3_icon1</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page3_icon2</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="pages_3_labels">
        <item > "Calendar, make the meet more intimate "</item>
        <item >"Turn your phone into a Wi-Fi hotspot"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages_3_desc">
        <item > "Open the calendar, set the schedule time, place, notice, etc. don't worry about missing the notice, intimate and convenient. "</item>
        <item > "Inconvenient to tell your home network password, and want to share the network with others?" Easily resolved through network hotspots. Open settings, click Wireless and Network-> Mobile network sharing, open the network hotspot. "</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="pages_4_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page4_icon1</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_launcher_foreground</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="pages_4_labels">
        <item >"Mobile Wireless Large screen"</item>
        <!--<item >"快速记录灵感"</item>-->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages_4_desc">
            <item > "Don't connect, put your phone screen on a TV or projector, whether it's an office demo, or play a game to watch a movie, and take you on a big screen experience." </item>
        <!--<item >"打开备忘录，随时随地记录您的重要事项 输入记录内容，点击创建笔记或创建待办。"</item>-->
    </string-array>


    <array name="pages_5_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page5_icon1</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="pages_5_labels">
        <item > "Handheld map, global navigation "</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages_5_desc">
        <item > "Open Google Maps, global travel, global navigation. Make travel better. "</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="pages_6_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page6_icon1</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page6_icon2</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="pages_6_labels">
        <item > "Face recognition, brush face unlock "</item>
        <item > "Cloud space, securely store your data "</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages_6_desc">
        <item > "Open settings, click Security and Privacy > Face unlock, follow the on-screen prompts to enter facial data. 2 After the entry is successful, pick up the phone to point to the face of the building, the screen will automatically light up and identify. You can unlock it by simply sliding the screen  "</item>
        <item > "Still worried about the loss of photos can not be recovered?" Open settings, sign in to Google Account, click on cloud Space and turn on cloud backup and other functions, the whole machine data can be automatically backed up, machine change easy recovery, cloud security storage, from this data more assured. "</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="pages_7_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page7_icon1</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page7_icon2</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page7_icon3</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page7_icon4</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="pages_7_labels">
        <item >"Manage Phone usage times"</item>
        <item > "Night mode, more comfortable with eyes "</item>
        <item > "The phone reads aloud the screen, the information is barrier-free "</item>
        <item >"Intercept nuisance calls or spam messages"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages_7_desc">
        <item > "Understand the use of your phone and apps, arrange screen time, and use your phone healthily." "</item>
        <item > "When the light is dark at night, watch the video or read for a long time, turn on eye care mode to relieve eye fatigue." "</item>
        <item > "You can also turn on the read-screen function by opening the settings, clicking Accessibility, and turning on the text-to-speech output switch. "</item>
        <item > "Turn on dialing, click > call block, select the type of phone or sms you want to intercept, you can effectively avoid harassing phone calls or spam messages." "</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="pages_8_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_page8_icon1</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="pages_8_labels">
        <item >"User manual"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages_8_desc">
        <item > "Want to get more detailed introduction and operation instructions for mobile phone features? User manuals are readily available. "</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
